Li Ming writes a report about clothes around the world.
李明写了一篇关于世界各地服装的报告
These people are wearing traditional clothes.
这些人身着传统服饰
Wow! Their clothes are so colourful.
哇   他们的衣服真是五颜六色
In some places, men wear skirts.
在有的地方   男人也穿裙子
How do they look?
他们看起来怎么样
This woman looks beautiful in her Sari.
这个妇女穿着莎丽真漂亮
A Sari is a traditional dress from India.
莎丽是印度传统服饰
Some people wear uniforms for work.
一些人工作时穿制服
These women look so pretty in black and white.
这些妇女身着黑白制服真漂亮
Many students wear school uniforms.
很多学生穿校服
Their uniforms look nice.
他们的校服真漂亮
Our school uniforms are blue and white.
我们学校的校服是蓝色和白色的
Do you have uniforms?
你有校服吗
What colours are they?
是什么颜色的